Why would the President want to kill your wife?
总统为何要杀死你的妻子
Her very existence is a threat to him.
她的存在是个威胁
So,you're telling me,he's so afraid of a scandal that he would commit murder.
总统为了掩盖丑闻会杀了她
Yes.
是的
This is crazy.
不可理喻
And,assassinating him,how does that even help you get his bone marrow?
行刺总统和你拿到骨髓有何关系
It was the only way to get near him.
只有这样我才能接近他
I needed allies,resources,people inside the White House to help arrange all this.
我需要盟友 资源 还有白宫内应的配合
So,we went to Kincaid's enemies.
我投靠了Kincaid的敌人
They were willing to assist,on the condition that we guaranteed his death.
他们想他死 只要我们保证行动成功
And,what about your team? Archer,Sandrine...
你的队友 Archer Sandrine他们
They're what,hired guns?
他们是雇佣兵?
Do they know all this?
他们知道内情吗
So you lie to them,too.
你隐瞒了事实
I told them what they need to know.
我只说了该说的部分
And I suggest you do the same with your family,especially Brian.
而且我建议你对你丈夫也一样
Do you trust how he'll react?
你相信他能正确理解此事?
You are out of your mind.
你疯了
Innocent people are dead because of you.
无辜的人因你而死去
I didn't want it to happen this way,but I'm in too deep.
我也不想这样 但事已至此
If I back out now,they'll get rid of me.
如果我退出 一样会死
And anybody else who's involved.
所有涉及此事的人
My family.
我的家人
And your family.
你的家人
You're an FBI agent,you can make a deal.
你是FBI探员 你可以做个交易
Go to the police,the prosecutors,there's a way out of this.
去投案 检方会给你出路
There isn't.
不可能
I can't stop this thing.
我不能停下
And neither can you.
你也是
Well,I don't accept that.
我不认同
What if I go to the President?
你觉得我去找总统如何
I'm meeting with his Chief of Staff tomorrow,I could tell him what's going on.
我明天会见幕僚长 我可以告诉他
I don't think so.
我想不可能了
The Chief of Staff just died of a heart attack an hour ago.
幕僚长一小时前心脏病发死了
The Chief of Staff,and now Hoffman's dead,too?
先是幕僚长 然后Hoffman也死了?
Just saw it on the news.
新闻看到的
Police believe he was the victim of an attempted carjacking.
警方认为 有人试图抢车
Hoffman I can understand. He was getting too close to the truth.
Hoffman我理解 他快发现真相了
But Creasy? Why'd they take him out?
但为何杀死Creasy
Creasy was never the boss.
Creasy不是幕后主脑
Maybe the people up the chain got cold feet.
也许更上层的人物害怕了
Decided to shut down the operation. Eliminate loose ends.
决定终止行动 把人灭口
If that's true,why aren't we dead?
如此事属实 我们为何未死
The night's still young.
夜还很长
Hoffman's murder wasn't a coincidence.
Hoffman的死不是巧合
I just spoke to the guy,he knew what was going on.
我刚跟他谈过 他知道发生啥事
Duncan and his friends are nervous and they took him out.
Duncan和他的同伙把人杀了
It's possible.
有可能
"It's possible"?
有可能?
Well,I don't think they would murder a federal agent.
我想他们不会杀死联邦探员
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
They just gunned down a teenager in our house.
他们刚在我们家杀了个年轻人
They'll do anything to get rid of the President.
他们为了杀死总统 会不惜一切
I have a feeling it's more complicated than that.
我觉得事情没那么简单
Why?
为何
I just do.
我感觉如此
I don't think they're terrorists.
他们不是恐怖分子
I think there's something else going on.
还有其他内情
This leaves us in a bad spot.
这让我们处境堪虞
We don't know who we're dealing with anymore.
我们无法得知对手
Logan's our only partner now.
Logan是我们唯一的同伙
Partner? I'm not so sure.
同伙? 我不能肯定
I don't like the fact that he didn't give us a heads up about Hoffman.
Hoffman的事情 他没有提前知会我们
Or Creasy.
还有Creasy
- It's not a good sign. - I'm meeting him tomorrow.
- 这不是好事 - 我明天会见他
- I'll get some answers then. - Just watch your step.
- 我试试套话 - 万事小心
- Ellen figured it out. - Excuse me?
- Ellen知道了 - 什么
Nina.
Nina
Her relationship to the President. The bone marrow.
她和总统的关系 骨髓的事情
The more people who know,the more complicated this becomes.
越多人知道 此事越麻烦
She's smart.
她很聪明
- She understands that. - I know she's smart.
- 她明白的 - 我知道她聪明
But will she keep her mouth shut?
但她会否三缄其口
Do you know something that you're not telling me?
你有否隐瞒了一些事情
- Like what? - I don't know. That's why I'm asking.
- 例如? - 不知道 所以我问你
Do you know why Duncan is doing this?
你知道Duncan这样做的原因?
No. I have no idea.
我不知道
One of my assistant's was there.
我一个助手在那里
She saw it with her own eyes,said it was horrible.
她说场面很可怖
Gasping and convulsing...
他的喘息和抽搐
I can't even think about his poor wife and their little girl.
他的遗孀和小女儿很可怜
It's tragic.
这是悲剧
I never cared for Quentin,but...
虽然我不喜欢Quentin
but any time a young man dies in the prime of his life...
但一个年轻人风华正茂就死去
Like Peter?
就像Peter?
Sort of.
差不多
What do you mean,"Sort of"?
差不多是什么意思
The truth is,Peter was partially responsible for his own death.
事实上 Peter的死部分咎由自取
You think it was Peter's fault that his plane crashed?
你觉得坠机是他的错?
It was his fault that he thought he was invincible and could fly a plane over the Rockies,at night,after 20 straight hours of campaigning.
他觉得自己无所不能
Don't look at me like that. I loved him as much as you did.
别这样看我 我一样很爱他
For God's sake,I practically raised him.
他是我养大的
But that doesn't mean we shouldn't be honest about what happened.
但我们必须承认那是事实
I agree.
我同意
The way that my sister compartmentalizes,and rationalizes,it's...
我姐对那件事情的定性和解释
It's infuriating. "Peter was too brash,so,he died."
简直难以容忍 Peter的死是咎由自取
There you go. As simple as that.
就这样 就这么简单
Well,she didn't want to face the truth.
她无法面对真相
It's just,I wanted to say to her,God,I wanted to tell her so badly,the reason Peter died is because your husband had him killed.
我真想告诉她 是你的丈夫杀了Peter
Well,I'm glad you restrained yourself.
幸好你克制住了
Here.
给你
It wasn't easy,I swear.
这不容易
Don't worry.
别担心
He'll pay for what he did.
他会付出代价
He better.
最好如此
- Are you losing faith? - I'm losing patience.
- 你灰心吗 - 正丧失耐性
And confidence.
还有信心
I still have no idea if this doctor is going to come through or if the FBI agent is doing his job.
我还是不明白为何我们要依靠 一个FBI探员和医生
Vanessa,what are you saying?
你想说什么
I'm saying it's time for us to get more involved.
我建议我们要介入此事
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Hostages Season 01 Episode 10
人质 第一季 第10集
I heard about our friend,Stan Hoffman.
我听说了Stan Hoffman的事情
Yeah. Sad. Another random act of violence.
很可惜 死于劫案
I thought we were going to take care of that together.
我以为我们说好一起动手
Clock was ticking. Had to take care of it myself.
没时间了 我必须自己来
Right.
好吧
- So,do you have the OR schematics? - No,not yet.
- 手术的安排如何 - 还没有
Security plan isn't final yet.
安保计划还在完善
Surgery's in five days.
还有5天就手术
I'll see what I can do.
我会设法
My contact had a heart attack last night. Who do I talk to now?
我的联系人心脏病死了 以后跟谁联系
Should I be insulted? You have me.
我不算? 你还有我
My deal was with Creasy. Not you.
我的交易方是Creasy 不是你
So,with all due respect,I need to know my side of this is being taken care of.
我想知道交易的条款还是否算数
If they want to reach out to you,they will.
他们要找你 自然会出面
Simple as that.
就这么简单
Oh,one more thing.
还有
The five minute window you requested in the operating room?
你要求在手术室里的5分钟
What about it?
怎样
It's getting harder to make those arrangements.
那样的安排很困难
That's non-negotiable.
这没得商量
Why do you need all that time?
你要那些时间做什么
We made a deal. I expect you and your partners to honor it.
这是交易的内容 希望你们信守承诺
I'll let them know.
我会转告
- I just talked to our friend at the FBI. - And?
- 我跟FBI的朋友谈过 - 怎样
He wants direct contact with you.
他希望跟你直接对话
It's not gonna happen. He talks to you.
不可能 他只对你
That's what I told him.
我也是这样说的
I got his cell number. You ready?
我搞到电话号码了 你准备好没
Go ahead.
说吧 202-555-0163
It's encrypted. I can't hack it.
加密了 我没法窃听
So how do we get access?
怎样才能搞定
We need a warrant.
要有授权
A warrant? What are you talking about,like going to a judge?
授权? 你说什么 要找法官?
Who said anything about a judge?
谁说找法官了
I said we need a warrant,I didn't say it needed to be real.
我说我们要授权 但没说是要真的
The President seems to be a reasonable man.
总统似乎很通情达理
Did you even try to approach him directly?
你有没有试过直接提出请求
I told you,that's not an option.
那根本不可能的
But how could you be so sure?
你怎能如此肯定
So,he had an illegitimate child. That was over 30 years ago.
他有个私生子 但已经过去30年了
Kincaid raped Nina's mother.
Kincaid强奸了Nina的母亲
What?
什么?
Kincaid was a young congressman at the time.
Kincaid是个年轻的国会议员
Nina's mother was a young journalist.
Nina的母亲是个记者
She went to his hotel room. For an interview.
她去他的酒店房间采访
And he raped her.
然后他强奸了她
A few weeks later,she threatened to go public with her story.
几周之后 她威胁要曝光此事
Kincaid tried to buy her silence.
Kincaid试图用钱让她封口
How could you possibly know all this?
你怎么知道这些
Burton Delaney was one of Kincaid's closest advisors.
Burton Delaney是Kincaid的智囊之一
35 Years Ago
35年前
He told me what happened next.
他跟我说了此事经过
I didn't force myself on her,Burton. Now,you believe me,right?
我没有强迫她 你相信我对吧
It's not about what I believe.
我相信与否不重要
It's about your reputation.
这关乎你的声望
Your political future.
你的仕途
You're on the cusp right now,Paul.
你现在处境不妙
This accusation could derail your entire career.
这项罪名会毁掉一切
I gave you the money to pay her off.
我给你钱去收买她
She wouldn't take it.
她不接受
Double the offer. Everyone has a price.
给她双倍 每个人都有价
Not this one.
这次不行
We need to take a different approach.
我们要试试别的办法
Well,what exactly are you saying?
你在说什么
I'm saying this is a problem that won't go away on its own.
问题是不会自己消失的
If you can't buy silence,you have to eliminate the source of the noise.
如果钱不行 那就只好将人解决掉
The woman's name was Kate Renner.
那个女人叫Kate Renner
Burton knew her.
Burton认识她
He couldn't go through with it,so...
他没法动手 所以
he helped her get out of the country.
他帮她出国
A few months later,he found out she was pregnant with Kincaid's child.
几个月之后 他发现她怀孕了
- Where is she now? - She died in childbirth.
- 她现在哪里 - 她死于难产
Burton adopted the girl.
Burton收养了那女孩
Nina. Raised her.
Nina 抚养她成人
He never told her or anybody else the truth.
我们没有告诉她真相
The only reason he told me is because...
他告诉我此事
because Nina got sick.
是因为Nina病了
So,now do you understand?
你现在明白了吗
Kincaid is not a reasonable man.
Kincaid并不通情达理
Hey,Boyd. It's Dad.
Boyd 是爸爸
Did you get my last message?
你收到我留言没
I haven't heard from you in a couple of days.
几天没有跟你联系了
Hey,call me back,buddy.
给我回电吧
Trying you again. Hey,call me back.
只是再试试 打给我
I'm sure you're fine,but,I'm getting worried.
我相信你很好 但我有点担心了
Okay? Talk soon. I love you.
稍后详谈 我爱你
You just found this phone?
你刚找到这手机?
Yeah,it must have fallen out of his pocket when he climbed in the window.
是 应该是他爬窗时掉出来的
But this is the first time I heard it ring,I swear.
这是我首次听到铃响 我发誓
Relax,I believe you.
别紧张 我相信你
What if Boyd's dad goes to the police? What are we gonna do?
如果Boyd的爸爸报警 我们该怎办
Maybe there's a medical solution.
也许还有其他疗法
If there were a medical solution,do you really think I'd be going through all this?
如果真的有 你以为我会这样做?
Let me review Nina's files,maybe I'll come up with something that...
让我看看Nina的资料 也许会有新发现
I've talked to the best oncologists in the world,Ellen.
我和世上最好的肿瘤学家谈过 Ellen
There are no other solutions.
没其他办法了
Look,I'm sure you're right.
我相信你是对的
But if I'm going to be standing over that man,watching him die on the operating table,
但要我坐视手术台上那男人死去
I can't be wondering if Nina could have been saved some other way.
我必须知道 这是救Nina唯一的办法
You're right.
你说得对
Read the files. Examine everything.
看看文件 检查清楚
You'll come to the same conclusion I did.
你的结论会跟我一样
I'll send over Nina's medical records to your office today.
我会把Nina的病历送去你办公室
Mr. President.
总统阁下
I'm afraid he was needed in another meeting.
他在参加另一个会议
Ted Jankowski. Acting Chief of Staff.
Ted Jankowski 代理幕僚长
It's nice to finally meet you.
幸会
- Something I can help you with? - yes,there might be.
- 请问有何贵干 - 这样
First of all,my condolences on Quentin.
请让我对Quentin的离世致哀
I met him a few times. Great loss.
我曾与他会面数次 很可惜
I need to speak with the President.
我需要面见总统
He and I were supposed to discuss a major policy initiative.
我们本应对一项重大 政策提案进行讨论
- What initiative? - I'm afraid it's classified.
- 什么提案 - 这是保密的
I'm sorry,but the President's schedule is fully booked.
抱歉 总统的日程已经满了
We can set something up for next week.
我们可帮你安排下周
This matter is time sensitive.
此事刻不容缓
Any chance I can get even a brief meeting on schedule sooner than that?
我必须在下周前向总统简报
Sorry,it's a busy week.
抱歉 总统这周很忙
- Ellen? - I found something in your wife's files.
- Ellen - 我在你妻子的文件里有所发现
1,249 people were tested,not one of them was a match.
当时检测了1249个人 没有人匹配
But there was one anonymous donor who came close.
但有个匿名捐赠者匹配率较高
How close?
多少
28%.
28%
So? That's not enough for a viable transplant.
这也不足以进行移植
I know,but this person could be a relative,maybe even a sibling.
我知道 但这个人可能是亲属 甚至是近亲
What I'm saying is,this person could lead us to a better match.
这个人也许能带我们找到 更合适的捐赠者
If there were a better match,we'd already know.
要是有 我早就发现
I'm trying to save your wife.
我在努力救你的妻子
What do you need?
你需要什么
Name and address.
姓名和住址
Give me the donor number.
告诉我电话号码
With Creasy gone,I've got no damn access.
Creasy死了 我连总统都见不了
You still think Kincaid will go public with OTI before the surgery?
你仍然觉得Kincaid会在手术前 将全信行动公诸于众吗
Possibly.
很有可能
- I don't know. - Why roll the dice?
- 我不知道 - 那为何冒险
- What are you saying? - OTI is important.
- 你在说什么 - 全信行动至关重要
Don't give this bastard a chance to take that away from you.
别给他机会将之夺走
Do we really want to bet the future of this country on Dr. Sanders?
我们真的要将这国家的未来 压在Sanders医生身上吗
Or Duncan Carlisle?
或是Duncan Carlisle
They tried and failed.
他们试过 但失败了
Why should we believe they'll pull it off this time?
我们凭什么相信 他们这次能成功?
Fair enough,but what other options do we have?
是有道理 但我们还有其他选择吗
It's not that easy to kill the President.
杀总统可不是易事
What did you find?
查到什么
The name of your mystery donor is Sally Whitaker.
匿名捐赠者叫Sally Whitaker
I'm texting you her address now.
我把她的住址短信给你
Okay,perfect. I'll let you know what I come up with.
好的 我会告诉你进展
Can I help you?
有何贵干
I'm looking for Sally Whitaker. Is she in?
我在找Sally Whitaker 她在吗?
I'm afraid she's not.
她不在
Do you know when she'll be back? I really need to speak with her.
请问她何时回来 我需要跟她谈谈
What for?
关于什么
Oh,I'm sorry,I'm with the Reston Blood Bank.
失礼了 我是列斯顿血库的
I tried calling a few times,but I couldn't get through.
我打过几次电话 但都没有接通
It's about a recent donation Sally made.
是关于Sally最近一次捐血
I have the paperwork here somewhere.
我这有文件证明
Do you mind if I come in for a moment?
我能进来吗
Okay.
好吧
But,you must have some kind of a mix-up.
但你肯定搞错了
Sally never mentioned anything about giving blood.
Sally从没提及她去过捐血
Are you sure? Our records indicate she did make a donation.
你确定吗 我们有她捐血的记录
It was earmarked for a very sick patient,Nina Carlisle?
是为了救治一位重病患者 Nina Carlisle
Never heard of her.
没听说过
Miss?
小姐
Are you all right?
你还好吗
Sorry,I just,that photo there...
抱歉 只是 那边的照片
It just looks like someone I know.
像是我认识的某人
Oh,yeah. Them.
是吗 他们
Yeah,they're,friends of my wife.
他们是我妻子的朋友
Okay,well,I'm sorry to have bothered you.
抱歉打扰了
Can I just trouble you for a glass of water?
能麻烦你给我杯水吗
I've been driving in the car all day,I just...
我开了一天的车 有点...
Sure.
没问题
Thank you.
谢谢
I understand the President's going to New York tomorrow.
总统明天要去纽约
- Do you have his full itinerary? - They just issued it to us.
- 你有他的行程安排吗 - 他们刚发过来
I'm talking about his unofficial itinerary.
我是说内部的行程
The one that includes his off-the-record meetings.
包括一些非官方安排
I will.
我会拿到
I'm on his detail tomorrow.
我明天负责他的出行
He'll have at least one off-the-record meeting tomorrow.
他至少会有一处私人会面
I want exact details. Time and place. Operational security.
我要所有细节 时间 地点以及安保情况
Everything.
全部资料
Copy that.
收到
Logan,one more thing.
Logan 还有件事
I'm gonna need you to get in touch with somebody.
我要你去见一个人
Hey,sweetie. I'm with customers,can I call you right back?
亲爱的 我现在有客人 稍后回电你好吗
Sorry,my name's Ellen.
抱歉 我叫Ellen
I found this phone in the street and just called the last number dialed.
我在街上捡到这个手机 这是最近拨出的号码
Oh,thanks so much,it belongs to my husband.
谢谢你 这是我丈夫的手机
Well,I just want to return it to the owner.
我想把电话还给失主
That's so nice of you. I can come get it wherever is convenient.
你真好人 我可以过来取
Well,I'm driving right now,where are you?
我正在开车 你在哪里
North Arlington. Near Wilson Boulevard and 20th.
北阿灵顿 靠近威尔逊和20大道
Well,I can drop it over to you if you like.
好的 我可以送过去给你
I have to head over there in about a half hour,anyway.
我反正顺路过去那边
Really? You're an angel. I'm in the antique store on the corner.
真的吗 你真好 我在街角的古董店里
See you soon.
稍后见
Yeah?
喂
- Raven gave me your number. - Okay,I'm listening.
- Raven让我联系你 - 你说吧
I'd like to meet in person.
我要和你见个面
- It's about a job opportunity. - Where's the party?
- 有工作给你 - 在哪里
I can tell you everything in person.
见面后再告诉你细节
But Raven said to let you know that it'd be a platinum level gig,platinum level pay.
但你要知道 这是白金级别的任务
Sounds good.
听起来不错
Meet me in 30 minutes at Mitchell Park.
30分钟后 米切尔公园见
- Southwest corner,I'll find you. - See you there.
- 在西南角 我会找到你 - 稍后见
What,did you use a fake warrant?
怎么 你用了假的授权?
Warrant was real. Signature was fake. Nobody ever looks.
授权是真的 签名是假的 反正没人会注意
- So,what's this phone call about? - I don't know.
- 这通电话什么意思 - 我不知道
You think it's anything to do with us?
你觉得跟我们有关吗
In the past 24 hours,a Secret Service agent and the Chief of Staff were killed.
过去24小时内 一个特勤局探员和幕僚长被杀
The fact that Logan's reaching out to some sort of operative?
现在Logan和某人联系谈任务
It's not good.
不是好事
I called you about your husband's phone.
我打过电话 关于你丈夫的手机
I'm just finishing up some paperwork,why don't you come on back?
我还有点文书工作 你先到后面来
You have some beautiful pieces here.
东西都很漂亮
Who the hell are you?
你是谁
Start talking.
说
Put the gun down. Please.
把枪放下 拜托
Who are you?
你是谁
I'm a doctor.
我是个医生
My husband called me.
我丈夫给我电话
I know you came to the house. You stole his phone.
我知道你去过我家 偷了他的手机
What do you want?
你想做什么
I know you're related to Nina Carlisle.
我知道你跟 Nina Carlisle有血缘关系
You two are a 28% match for bone marrow type.
你们的骨髓有28%的匹配度
Trust me,you don't want to get involved in this.
相信我 你不想介入此事
I saw the wedding photo in your hall.
我看见你家门厅的结婚照
If you knew what was good for you,you'd leave and never come back.
如果你是个聪明人 就马上离开
Well,I can't do that.
我不能
I know who you are.
我知道你是谁
You're Kate Renner.
你是Kate Renner
Nina's mother.
Nina的母亲
I haven't heard that name in many years.
我很多年没听到这个名字了
Why are you here?
你为何来此
Burton Delaney.
Burton Delaney
He told me your story,I'm sorry.
他告诉了我你的事情 我很遗憾
It was a lifetime ago.
那是很久以前的事了
I've moved on.
我已经重新开始
I thought you were dead.
我以为你死了
That was the idea.
本来是这样安排的
Must have been hard.
你肯定很艰难
Giving up your child.
要离开你的孩子
What do you want?
你想怎样
Your daughter is sick.
你女儿生病了
She has leukemia.
白血病
She needs a donor.
她需要骨髓移植
You're not a close enough match,but I was hoping you could lead me to one.
你和她匹配度不够 但我想通过你找到合适的人
If Nina has one other blood relative,there's a chance.
如果Nina还有其他近亲 就还有希望
Did you ever have any other children?
你还有其他孩子吗
No.
没有
I see.
我明白了
Well,I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
抱歉打搅了
Why is Nina's life so important to you?
为何你这么在乎Nina的生死
Because...
因为...
I have a family too.
我也有家庭
Hi,can I help you?
有何贵干
Yes,I'm John Norton.
我是John Norton
Boyd's father.
Boyd的父亲
Oh,right.
好的
Boyd. Right okay.
Boyd 对
I'm Brian Sanders. Come on in.
我是Brian Sanders 请进
Nice to meet you.
幸会
Morgan's told me all about your son.
Morgan跟我说过你的儿子
Oh,well...
这个
I'm sure you heard the news.
我想你已经知道了
No,I haven't. Everything okay?
不 我不清楚 一切还好吗?
Not exactly.
不太好
I'm afraid,Boyd...
恐怕Boyd...
Well,he broke up with your daughter in a rather cowardly manner.
很怯懦地和你的女儿分手了
Okay.
好吧
Well,listen,not to worry.
听着 别担心
Boys that age tend to not have the highest emotional IQs.
这个年纪的男孩情商都不是很高
Yeah,I agree.
是的 我同意
That's why I'm here.
所以我过来
I'd like to talk to Morgan,in person.
我想亲自和Morgan谈谈
I feel I owe it to her.
我觉得对她有所亏欠
Okay. Sure.
好的 当然
Morgan!
Morgan
This is Mr. Norton.
这位是Norton先生
Boyd's dad.
Boyd的爸爸
We've met.
我们见过
Hello,Mr. Norton.
你好 Norton先生
Hi,Morgan.
你好 Morgan
Nice to see you,I...
很高兴见到你
wish it were under different circumstances.
如果不是现在这种情况就更好了
I felt I needed to come over and apologize to you on my son's behalf.
我觉得有必要过来 为我儿子的不当行为而道歉
That's so sweet of you,but you didn't have to do that.
你很体贴 但其实没必要
I'm fine.
我没事
Really,I'm okay.
真的 我没事
I'm confused.
我不明白
I'm sorry,Mr. Sanders,I thought you knew.
抱歉 Sanders先生 我以为你知道
Look,I heard from Boyd about an hour ago.
一小时前我接到Boyd的回复
He told me everything.
他告诉我所有事
This is no ordinary target.
这不是一般的目标
He's a man,like any other.
他就跟普通人一样
You pull the trigger,you get paid.
干掉目标 你就能收钱
I want double what you're offering.
我要双倍酬劳
I can go back with that.
我可以答应
Anything else?
还有什么
Yeah,I pick my team.
我挑选我的团队
Okay.
可以
I'll reach out to you later today with more details.
稍后我会告知你详细情况
Come to think of it,I do have one question.
另外 我还有个问题
Why?
为什么
It's okay,Mr. Norton. My parents know that I got pregnant.
没事 我父母知道我怀孕了
Boyd shouldn't have run out on his responsibilities.
Boyd不应该逃避责任
I mean,now is not the time to ship out on a fishing boat for three months.
现在可不是出海远航的时机
Well,he's been talking about that for a long time.
他有这个想法很长时间了
I know.
我知道
He has no idea how hard the work's gonna be.
他不知道会有多辛苦
Well,I don't blame him...
我不怪他
Mr. Norton,and I certainly don't blame you.
Norton先生 我也不怪你
I appreciate that,Morgan.
谢谢你 Morgan
Really,I do.
真的
But you know,it's not really Boyd's fault.
请你理解 这不是Boyd的错
The truth is,I should have set a better example.
事实上 我没有做一个更好的榜样
I wasn't around enough when he was growing up.
他小时候我不常在他身边
It was nice to see you again,Morgan.
见到你很高兴
Guess my son has a lot of growing up to do.
我想我的儿子还不够成熟
I need your help. Take a look at this photo.
我需要你 帮忙查查这照片
Who are they?
他们是谁
The guy on the right is our contact inside the Secret Service.His name's Logan.
右边那个是我们在特勤局的内应 叫Logan
He met up with that other guy about a half an hour ago.
一小时前他见了另外一个人
Duncan wants to know who he is.
Duncan想知道这人的身份
I'll run it through facial recognition. See if we get a hit.
我会通过面部识别系统查查 希望有结果
Are you okay?
你没事吧
Yeah,I'm fine.
我没事
What happened with Sally Whitaker?
Sally Whitaker什么情况
She's Nina's mother.
她是Nina的母亲
What?
什么?
Sally Whitaker's real name is Kate Renner.
Sally Whitaker的真名是Kate Renner
Are you positive?
你肯定?
Yes,I...
是的
I saw a picture of you and Nina.
我见到你和Nina的合照
In her house.
在她家里
And I confronted her and...
而且我跟她谈过
she confirmed everything you said about Kincaid.
她确认了你关于Kincaid的说辞
She's been living under an assumed identity all these years.
这些年她一直使用假身份
Why didn't you tell me?
你为何不告诉我
What good would it have done for me to tell you?
我告诉你有何好处
You don't think Nina would have wanted to know her mother was alive?
你不觉得Nina想知道她母亲还在世?
Of course she would have. That's why I had to lie.
当然她想知道 所以我要隐瞒
You think I wanted to keep this secret? I did it to protect everybody.
你以为我想保守秘密? 我是为了保护大家
Nina,Kate,Sawyer.
Nina Kate Sawyer
- You could have told me. - I could have.
- 你可以告诉我 - 是可以
But then what?
但那又如何
You'd be forced to lie to your wife every day for the rest of your life.
你要每天都对你太太撒谎
I carried that burden with me since she was born.
从她出生那天起我就这样做
Trust me.
相信我
I did you a favor,Duncan.
你不会想那样
You know I always thought of you like a son.
你知道我视你如子
I know you have.
我知道
So I'm gonna ask you one time.
我要再问你一次
Is there anything else you haven't told me?
你是否还有事情隐瞒
- Excuse me? - I don't want any more surprises.
- 什么? - 我不希望再有惊喜
I've told you everything.
我都告诉你了
Duncan,it's me.
Duncan 是我
What is it?
什么事
Kramer took a photo of a guy talking to the Secret Service agent.
那个跟特勤局探员交谈的人
You got a name?
你查到名字了?
Robert Harper. Former Army Ranger and decorated sniper.
Robert Harper 退役游骑兵 授勋的狙击手
Sniper?
狙击手?
Four tours of duty in Iraq.
在伊拉克服役四次
Over 100 confirmed kills.
超过100次狙杀目标
Duncan.
Duncan
What is it?
什么事
The guy Logan was talking to in the park.
Logan在公园见的那人
He's a sniper.
是个狙击手
They want to take me out.
他们想杀死我
They did the math and decided that it was just too risky to continue the operation.
他们认为继续行动风险太大
- Creasy,Hoffman. - Now me.
- Creasy Hoffman - 现在是我
They're mopping up.
他们要杀人灭口
- You should get out of the country. - No.
- 你要出国避避 - 不
- We've come too far. - So,what do you propose?
- 我们介入太深 - 你有何打算
Shoot the sniper before he shoots me.
先把那个狙击手干掉
What the hell just happened back there with Boyd's father?
刚才你和Boyd的父亲怎么回事
I found Boyd's phone.
我找到Boyd的手机
And his Dad kept calling,
他爸一直打过来
so Sandrine and I texted him back.
Sandrine和我发了短信
We made up a cover story,so that Mr. Norton wouldn't go to the cops.
编造了一个故事 让Norton先生不会去报警
What?
什么
I can't believe you. When were you going to tell me this?
难以置信 你打算何时告诉我?
We didn't know he was going to come over.
我们不知道他会过来
"We"? Hey. We're not on the same side,Morgan.
我们? 那不是自己人
We have to cooperate with them.
我们要跟他们合作
- Besides... - Besides what?
- 再者 - 什么
They didn't mean to kill Boyd.
他们不是有意杀死Boyd
It just... happened.
那只是意外
Oh,for God sakes. Morgan,listen.
老天 Morgan
These people are holding us hostage.
他们把我们一家劫持为人质
They're evil. You see that,don't you?
他们是坏人 你懂吗
- How are you feeling? - Optimistic.
- 你怎么样 - 很乐观
Now,frankly,I never liked the idea of sitting back and relying on somebody else. I'm a Marine at heart.
我也不喜欢躲于幕后 玩弄阴谋诡计 我内心是海军
- Only happy in the mud. - But you clean up so well.
- 喜欢在泥潭里搏斗 - 但你衣冠楚楚
You can't have dirt on your shoes in the oval office?
你甚至不会让泥沾染你的皮鞋
That is why I have you to keep me civilized.
那是因为你让我变得彬彬有礼
Not too civilized.
也别太有礼
What about that FBI agent?
那个FBI探员怎样了
Carlisle.
Carlisle
- I'm handling it. - Good.
- 我会处理 - 很好
I'm worried about Morgan.
我担心Morgan
She's starting to believe these guys.
她开始相信那些人
What do you mean?
什么意思
She helped them cover up Boyd's death.
她帮他们掩盖Boyd的死
It's like she's...
就像她
part of their team.
变成了同伙
She told me what happened.
她跟我说了
I don't understand why you're so upset with her.
我不明白你为何焦虑
What do you mean you don't know why?
你有什么不明白
I think she did the right thing,given the circumstances.
我想她做得对 别无选择
We're in too deep. We no longer have the privilege of being...
我们介入太深 已经无法...
- moralistic. - What the hell does that mean?
- 遵守道德 - 这什么意思
I think your initial instinct was right.
我想你最初的直觉是对的
- Initial instinct? - That I should do what they want.
- 最初的直觉 - 我们应该听命行事
I know I told you to cooperate,but you were the one who had the strength to say no.
我知道我曾这样说过 但是你决心反抗
You fought back.
你做到了
I admire that about you. You made the right choice.
我觉得很了不起 你做得对
Did I?
是吗
Too many people have died since then. You almost died.
因为这样 太多人死了 你也差点死了
All to save one man?
就为了救一个人?
No,I'm not willing to sacrifice our family for the life of Paul Kincaid.
我不想为了救Paul Kincaid 而牺牲我的家人
Where is that coming from?
你这个想法怎么来的
Nowhere.
我自己想的
It's just a decision that I have to make.
只是我下的决心
That's Duncan talking.
那是Duncan的语气
- What? - He's been manipulating us from the start.
- 什么 - 他一直在操控我们
You gotta let me in. We gotta be together on this.
我们应该一起面对 团结一致
If I do what he wants,then we're free.
只要我做了 我们就自由了
We cannot trust him.
我们不能相信他
I disagree.
我不认同
The guy was hard to track down but I got an address for you.
这个人很难追踪行迹 但我找到个地址
Thanks.
谢谢
- Do you need any help? - No,I got it.
- 你需要帮忙吗 - 不
And thanks for sticking around.
谢谢你还留在这里
Archer was right about you.
Archer说得对
You're good.
你很优秀
I'll take care of the sniper tonight.
我今晚会搞定那个狙击手
*******
1小时内 来加士坚和史密夫大道见我
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
- 怎么了 - 没事
I...
我
It's about my kid.
我孩子有些事
Well,go. I'll cover for you.
去吧 我帮你顶着
Thanks.
谢谢
BOARDING PASS ******
登机牌
What do you want?
你想怎样
This was in Boyd's pocket.
这东西在Boyd的口袋里
Guess he meant it for you.
我想他准备给你的
Where did you bury him?
你把他埋在哪里
Don't think about that. Just keep the ring.
别想太多 留着那戒指就好
Did you kill him?
你杀了他?
I went to his apartment,but he wasn't there.
我去了他的寓所 没人
He's on a plane to New York City right now.
他在去纽约的飞机上
If he's trying to kill you,why is he on his way to New York?
如果他要杀你 去纽约做什么
Because I'm not the target.
我不是目标
The President is.
总统才是
He's scheduled to be in New York all day tomorrow.
明天他计划前往纽约
The question is,where and when?
问题是 下手的时机
How are they planning to take him out?
究竟如何动手
Glad you could make it.
很高兴你肯来
- Where's my son? - Safe and sound. With his father.
- 我儿子在哪里 - 很安全 和父亲在一起
Call him if you don't believe me.
如果你不信可以打电话
I just needed to make sure you'd show.
我只是要确保你出现
What do you want?
你想怎样
I have a business proposition for you.
我有个交易提议
Low risk. High reward.
低风险 高回报
My kid is the one who believes in fairy tales.
我的儿子才会信这些童话
Not me.
我不会
I need a friend inside Duncan's operation.
我需要在Duncan身边有个朋友
A friend?
朋友?
You're talking to the wrong girl.
你找错人了
Okay,a spy.
好了 内应
Better?
没错吧
What are you offering?
你开什么价
He spends the morning at the UN,but security there is far too tight.
他早上在联合国 但安保太严密
Lunch and photos at the New York Stock Exchange and then a meeting at the Federal Reserve.
在纽约证交所合照和午餐 和联储局开会
Both hard targets.
都很难下手
Doesn't seem viable.
不太可能
Here.
这里
At 5:30,the President has scheduled a meeting with Mike Petrocelli,head of the Teamsters.
5:30 总统和卡车工会主席 Mike Petrocelli会面
That meeting is a fiction.
这是个掩眼法
How do you know?
你怎么知道
Kincaid's got the unions in his pocket for years,and he hates Petrocelli,he's not wasting an hour with him.
Kincaid一直有工会的支持 而且他讨厌Petrocelli
Unless it's an election year.
这又不是选举年
So where do you think he's going?
那他会去哪里
To church.
教堂
What?
什么
When I was in his camp,
我还在他团队中时
he always stopped by St. Theodore's when he was in New York.
每次在纽约他都去圣西奥多教堂
The church is on Broadway and 24th,which is five minutes away from his 4:30 meeting.
教堂在百老汇和24街之间 离他4:30的会议地点5分钟路程
- You think that's where he's going to be? - I do.
- 你认为他会去 - 是的
And it's the perfect place to take him out.
这是动手的好时机
If they succeed,Nina dies.
如果他死了 Nina也会死
Then we need to get there first.
我们要先下手为强
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-------------------------- 本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用 禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负 --------------------------